

Madeline Johnston

Portfolio - maddyjohnston.github.io Email - maddy.johnston@sky.com Mobile - 07443337509

Profile

I'm a final year BA architecture student studying at Plymouth University with a goal to become a fully qualified architect and advance my skills by working alongside professionals. My positive attitude and confidence within the course was personally acknowledged by the Year 1 program leader after being invited to work as a student ambassador for my faculty. This continued into my second year where I was also selected to guide students in the new digital fabrication suite. My previous job at Morrison's as a Customer Assistant taught me many valuable skills, including interpersonal communication skills with customers and the ability to deal with difficult situations professionally. The retail environment has given me experience with working as part of a team, and using my initiative when working by myself. I have transferred these skills into my degree programme, working in group projects and individual design projects.

Education

Ba(hons) Degree | Plymouth University | 2015 - Present

Architecture - (Provisional) 2:1

A-Level | South Downs College | 2013-2015

Maths - B

Fine Art - C

Philosophy - D

GCSE | Oaklands Catholic School | 2008—2013

3A*, 6A's, B, C - Including 2A*'s in Maths and an A in English

Experience

Student Ambassador | Plymouth University | 2016 - Present

- Setting up and organising the studio for open days
- Providing information about the course to prospective students
- Guiding prospective students through creative workshops

Customer Assistant | Morrisons | Sep 2014 - Sep 2015

- Serve customer in a friendly and helpful manner
- Complete tasks on shop floor to a high standard
- Deliver efficient and accurate service to all customers

Work Experience | Pick Everard | July 2014

- One week building engineers learning CAD and information about BREEAM
- Second week with architects designing a beach side home

Work Experience | PWP Architects | July 2011

- Two weeks shadowing site visits and working on demo projects

Skills

- Strong interpersonal communication skills
- Ambitious and willing to learn
- Experience of leadership and efficient teamworking skills
- Good time management and organisational skills
- Full, clean UK driving licence.

Software

AutoCAD			
Photoshop			
InDesign			
Rhinoceros			
Revit			
123D Design			
123D Make			

References

Toshiko Terazono

Lecturer in Architecture, Year 1 Leader, Room 204 RLB PL48AA toshiko.terazono@plymouth.ac.uk

Alejandro Veliz Reyes

Lecturer in Architectural Digital Design, Room 401 RLB PL48AA alejandro.velizreyes@plymouth.ac.uk